Zachary Bohn Developer and Designer

Professional Summary

I am a meticulous developer and designer, focused on design and development of impactful user experiences. I am currently a Creative Technology and Design masters student, where I am concentrating on web development, user experience design, and creative technologies. Previously, I worked in product strategy and marketing research and cofounded Helena.org. To see my work please visit www.zacharybohn.com.

Experience

Seminaut Game Studios

Oct 2022 - Present

Design Technologist Intern

· Leading team of three engineers and two designers to build Seminaut's design system and front-end component library

ZS Associates

Nov 2020 - Jan 2022

Strategy, Insights, and Planning Associate

- Completed ten projects helping companies with marketing research and product strategy, including:
 - Defined customer personas based on distinct characteristics and created messaging that resonated with each persona, resulting in successful launch

Simon-Kucher and Partners

Nov 2019 - Nov 2022

Consultant (Oct-Jun) | Innovation Associate (Jun-Oct)

- UX research, prototyping, and business case development for internal start-up, leading to successful launch
- Co-founded social impact group with 20 members

Parakeet Health

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

Chief Executive Officer and UX Designer

- Led team of 5 to create high-fidelity prototype design activities included personas, customer journey map, wireframes, brand guidelines, and high-fi mock-ups
- Business pitch and prototype placed first in USC Health Systems Innovation Collaborative Challenge, a \$10K entrepreneurship competition

Helena.org

Apr 2015 - Mar 2017

Cofounder

- · Created and validated concept through user interviews, recruited members, developed brand, and created fundraising documents, resulting in more than \$21M raised to date
- Helena.org has moved more than 37 million pieces of PPE to hospitals and health workers to help with COVID-19

Contact Information

Portfolio: www.zacharybohn.com Email: zacharybohn1@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/zacharymbohn

Skills

Development

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

React

Responsive UI

SASS

Three.js

P5.js

SQL(some)

Python(some)

Flask(some)

Design

Figma

Sketch

Rapid Prototyping

Interaction Design

UX Research

Education

University of Colorado at Boulder M.S. Creative Technology and Design

2022 - 2024 | GPA: TBD

Graduate Courses (First Year): Creative Coding, Front-End Development II, Design Methods, UX Design, Design Studio, Programming and Data Structures, CSS for Javascript Developers

University of Southern California B.S. Business Administration 2019 | GPA: 3.6

Honors: Global Student Entrepreneurship Award, Lime Fellow, USC Continuing Student Scholarship, Cum Laude

Supplemental Education

Harvard Extension Intensive Introduction to Computer Science 2022 | GPA: 4.0

The App Brewery The Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2022